<versions>
  <dlcs>mmh_all_logs.zip;48;$2;heads/block/all_logs_acacia_log_horizontal.json,mmh_all_woods;22;$1;heads/block/acacia_wood.json,mmh_all_shulker_boxes;17;$1;heads/block/red_shulker_box.json,mmh_copper_golems.zip;4;$1;heads/entity/copper_golem_exposed.json</dlcs>
  <release>
    <version>1.20_1.0.43</version>
    <notes>D1    Added new config option to disable dlc nag for OPs. also reduced chance of being nagged.
D2    Fixed viewheads command, fixed exception with zombie_villager.
D3    Added a default head to handle missing head files, called Head not found with a pink and black pattern.
D4    Fixed initlization of ArrayList. Added new config sub command, and permission moremobheads.config.
D5    Switched to IntelliJ. Added subcommand Chance with subcommands Export/Import that creates an entity_chances.json
    for batch updating entity chances. DevBuilds now have a 60 day time limit for usage.
D6    Optimized Wandering Trader trade selection to fix server hangs.
D7    Started standardizing MMH to optimize code. Updated MMH Library to work with 1.21.8-1.21.9
D8    Added MobHeadDropEvent for developers.
D9    Added CoreUtils Library. Added Exploding bed damage as WeaponType for beheading messages.
D10    Added new features to 1.20 eventHandler for parity. Streamlined code for quicker fixes and updates.
D11    Added copper_golem, finished streamlining code. Fixed Black Horse Head.</notes>
    <link>https://dev.bukkit.org/projects/moremobheads2/files</link>
  </release>
  <developer>
    <version>1.20_1.0.44.D13</version>
    <notes>D1 Switched from disabling plugin on load of unsupported MC Version to attempt to load newest eventHandlers
    D2  Console can now use mmh config, tabs auto-fixed, added config_comments.yml guide, config.yml now clean
    D3  Fixed beheading messages (hex/gradient/rainbow), added 10 new colorful ones, now supports up to 8-color gradients,
    fixed Zombie Villager Shepherd + biome heads, updated head updater, CoreUtils sync
    D4  Fixed Vex handler, Fixed Villager.json
    D5  Fixed Villager and Zombie Villager for Paper.
    D6  Fixed Cat and Frog heads.
    D7  Fixed updatechecker message on join, via CoreUtils update.
    D8  Fixed Copper Golem weatherstate detection.
    D9  Fixing papers changes to weatherstate. Reset epoch time to 1764860848L.
    D10 Fixed NPE when Creaking dies without a cause.
    D11 Added 1.21.11 Mobs
    D12 Updated translation system, and updated epoch time.
    D13 Added rest of translations, fixed Config GUI not reloading on close, fixed named weapons being called bare hands.</notes>
    <link>https://dev.bukkit.org/projects/moremobheads2/files</link>
  </developer>
</versions>
